Finding Aid for the Lamar Alexander Papers - Photographs
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Series I: Governor’s Papers
  - Photographs, Chronological
    - Souvenir Program from 1951 National Governor’s Convention; Proclamations; Driver’s License Testing Center Opening, July 13, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Tennessee Junior Livestock Exposition, July 15, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Tourism Photos; Robots on Legislative Plaza, July 16, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Lamar Alexander and Alex Haley in Henning, Tennessee, July 17, 1982 (Box 8)
    - July 20-21, 1982 (2 Folders) Planning Farm Program, Visits to Farms and Farmers; Producers of Tennessee-Made Movie; Basic Skills Conference (Box 8)
    - Governor’s Task Force on Small Business, July 22, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Farm Visit, July 29, 1982 (Box 8)
    - (Contact Sheets), July 30, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Lamar Alexander and UT Football Coach Johnny Majors, August 4, 1982 (Box 8)
    - (2 Folders) Groundbreaking for Expansion of American Can Company, Shelbyville; Tennessee Safety Conference, August 11, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Highway Patrolmen Bravery Ceremony, Jackson, August 12, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Groundbreaking for Expansion of Ferro Manufacturing Plant, Pikeville, August 16, 1982 (Box 8)
    - (5 Folders) Middle/Southeast Tennessee Flood Damage; Views of Flood Damage from Helicopter, Hamilton County; County Farm Bureau President’s Conference, August 18, 1982 (Box 8)
    - (Contact Sheets), August 19, 1982 (Box 8)
    - (2 Folders) Discussion of Minority-Owned Business Programs; Computer Presentation; Proclamations; Service Awards, August 20, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Observance of Perinatal Week; Associated Builders and Contractors Proclamation, August 24, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Lamar Alexander Meets with Officers of the Tennessee Vocational Agriculture Teacher’s Association, August 5, 1982 (Box 8)
  - Photographs, Chronological
    - Bartlett High School Assembly; Swearing in of Judges; Meeting in Memphis, September 1, 1982 (Box 9)
    - Lamar Alexander and Howdy Doody; Proclamations, September 9, 1982 (Box 9)
    - (3 Folders) West Tennessee Flood Damage, Helicopter Tour, September 14, 1982 (Box 9)
    - (2 Folders) Southern Governor’s Task Force on Drugs with Florida Gov. Robert Graham; United Food and Commercial Workers Shop Stewards Conference, September 15, 1982 (Box 9)
    - Signing for the Purchase of Tennessee Crops by China, Press Conference; Proclamations, September 21, 1982 (Box 9)
    - Knowles Center for Senior Citizens, Tax Relief for the Elderly, September 23, 1982 (Box 9)
    - Celebrity Exhibition Softball Game, September 28, 1982 (Box 9)
    - Teledyne Lewisburg Building, October 1, 1982 (Box 9)
    - Lamar Alexander Leads Vietnam Veterans Recognition Day Parade, October 3, 1982 (Box 9)
    - Inauguration of Dr. David Satcher as President of Meharry Medical College, October 4, 1982 (Box 9)
    - Parade Magazine Published at Dickson Plant, October 5, 1982 (Box 9)
    - (3 Folders) Service Merchandise Groundbreaking; Entertainment Expo at Municipal Auditorium; Luncheon Address at 30th Annual Tennessee Governor’s Conference on Economic and Community Development, October 7, 1982 (Box 9)
    - Country Music Association’s 16th Annual Awards Show, October 11, 1982 (Box 9)
    - (Contact Sheets), October 14, 1982 (Box 9)
    - Lamar Alexander with Alex Haley and John Rice, Museum of Appalachia Homecoming, October 17, 1982 (Box 9)
    - Lamar Alexander with Clayburn Peeples and District Attorney General William Kinton, October 19, 1982 (Box 9)
    - 70th Birthday Party Celebration for Minnie Pearl, October 25, 1982 (Box 9)
    - (Contact Sheet), October 26, 1982 (Box 9)
    - Election Night ‘82, November 2, 1982 (Box 9)
    - Staff Luncheon at Residence with Honey and Lamar Alexander, November 3, 1982 (Box 9)
    - (2 Folders) Safety Commissioner Gene Roberts, November 23, 1982 (Box 9)
    - Family Decorating Christmas Tree, December 1, 1982 (Box 9)
    - News Conference about Japanese Manufacturing Plant Moving to Tennessee, December 15, 1982 (Box 9)
    - (Contact Sheets), December 21, 1982 (Box 9)
    - Christmas, 1982 (Box 9)
  - Photographs, Chronological
    - Sumner County Community Day, January 4, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Jobs Skills Task Force, January 6, 1983 (Box 10)
    - (Contact Sheets), January 12, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Honey Alexander in Inaugural Gown; Lamar Alexander at Piano, January 13, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Swearing In, January 14, 1983 (Box 10)
    - (5 Folders) Inauguration: Reception, Parade, Ball, Sunday Brunch, Church, January 15, 1983 (Box 10)
    - (Contact Sheets), January 17, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Charlie Daniels Day Proclamation; Additional Proclamations, January 18, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Job Training Coordinating Council, January 20, 1983 (Box 10)
    - (Contact Sheets), January 25, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Certificate of Election, January 27, 1983 (Box 10)
    - (Contact Sheets), February 2, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Vocational Education Week, February 7, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Savings and Loan Week, February 22, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Proclamations, February 23, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Budget Address, House Chamber, March 1, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Victor Ashe, Farragut Hills Elementary School, March 2, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Conference, March 3, 1983 (Box 10)
    - (Contact Sheets), March 4, 1983 (Box 10)
    - The Nashville Network Launch; Lamar Alexander Testifying on Master Teaching Legislation, March 7, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Rep. Zane Whitson, March 8, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Jim Henry and Beauty Queens; Meeting, March 10, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Susan Simons Headshots, March 11, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Richard Fulton and Mrs. Jolly at Residence, March 14, 1983 (Box 10)
    - 100th Anniversary Celebration of Jamison Bedding; Stephanie Chivers Headshots; Debbie Tate Headshots, March 15, 1983 (Box 10)
    - FFA State Officers, March 16, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Master Teachers Press Conference, March 17, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Employee Headshots, March 18, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Sure Shot Rabbit Hunters Supper; Local Government Day; Tennessee Taxpayers Association Board of Directors Meeting, March 22, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Proclamations, March 23, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Lamar Alexander with The Shirt Shop Photo Contest T-Shirt; Senator Pearson and St. Ann’s School, Bartlett; Human Services Open House, March 24, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Press Conference, March 28, 1983 (Box 10)
    - 36th Annual Tennessee 4-H Congress; Republican Women, March 29, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Swearing in of Susan Simons; Minister Ray Robinson and Confirmation Class, March 30, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Ben Longley and Maytag Executives; Ned McWherter in Office; Representative Chris Turner and Highland Heights Baptist Church Group, March 31, 1983 (Box 10)
  - Photographs, Chronological
    - Interim Master Teacher Commission Announcement, Bill Willis, Russ French, April 1, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Tennessee Master Teaching Program Briefing with Ronald Reagan; League for the Hearing Impaired, April 4, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Miss Tennessee; The Governor’s Prayer Breakfast, April 5, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Dresden Elementary School; Victor Ashe and Farragut Middle School, April 6, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Lunch with Middle Tennessee Newspaper Editors; Susan Richardson and Republican Women; Honey Alexander and Commissioner Ruett, April 11, 1983 (Box 11)
    - (Contact Sheets), April 12, 1983 (Box 11)
    - “Dear Governor, Please ‘Bee’ Mulish About Our Education” Banner and Meeting; Students on Capitol Steps, April 13, 1983 (Box 11)
    - April 19-20, 1983 Rep. Clyde Webb Presents a Drawing to Governor; Representatives Pickering and David L. Ussery and Students (Box 11)
    - Senator Person and Christ Methodist Church Day School; Senator Victor Ashe; Representative Benny Stafford and Alcoa High School; Better Schools Task Force; West Tennessee Jobs Conference, April 21, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Brandywine Farms Homeowners Association Meeting; Lamar Alexander and Judge Beech, April 25, 1983 (Box 11)
    - (Contact Sheets), April 26, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Proclamations; Franklin School Students; Bill Signing; Presentation of Portrait, April 27, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Joe Davis, Mr. Hagusa and Sharp Representatives, April 28, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Opening of “Made in Tennessee” Exhibition, Tennessee State Museum, May 3, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Mississippi Queen Gala, Memphis, May 5, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Jere Griggs, Lin Tsun-hsiun, Director of the Coordination Council on North American Affairs, May 10, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Ashland City Students; Tommy Milam and Legislative Intern Group, May 11, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Bill Signing HB 480/SB 501, Representative Randy McNally and Representative Elkins; Governor’s Small Business Conference, May 12, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Linn Yann, Cambodian Superspeller, May 16, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Swearing in of Hubert McCullough, Jr., Commissioner of the Department of Finance and Administration; St. Pius X School Students; St. Vincent DePaul School Students, May 17, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Swearing in of Jim Word; Presentations to Governor, May 19, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Swearing in (unknown individuals), June 2, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Conference and Banquet, June 3, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Hanging of Pictures, June 6, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Computer Familiarization Seminar, Computer Class; Remarks at State Fairgrounds, Fan Fair, June 7, 1983 (Box 11)
    - News Conference Promoting Child Safety with Lamar and Honey Alexander and Dick Van Patten, June 8, 1983 (Box 11)
    - (2 Folders) Tennessee Master Teacher Program with Ronald Reagan, Knoxville, June 14, 1983 (Box 11)
    - National Sheriff’s Association Annual Informative Conference Opening Session, June 20, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Celebrity Softball Classic; 4-H Group, June 22, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Proclamations, June 23, 1983 (Box 11)
    - (Contact Sheets), June 29, 1983 (Box 11)
    - State Comptroller William Snodgrass Receives Distinguished Service Award; TN Student Assistance Board, June 30, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Child’s Birthday Party; Miss Tennessee, July 8, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Clean Water Briefing, Ned McWherter, John Wilder, July 11, 1983 (Box 11)
    - TEMA Sequoyah Drill; Helicopter Tour, July 14-15, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Quilts, July 25, 1983 (Box 11)
  - Photographs, Chronological
    - Reporters’ Children, August 11, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Caldwell with Minnie Pearl, August 19, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Conference, September 2, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Tourism Promotion; Young Bridgestone Executives from Japan; Better Schools Advisory Board Meeting, September 7, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Governor Alexander Presents Outstanding Achievement Awards to Four Tennessee Teachers who received the Presidential Award for Excellence in Science and Mathematics Teaching, September 16, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Enrichment Forum, September 21, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Tennessee Forum on Education Excellence, Vanderbilt University, September 23, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Mayor Fulton and Auto Emission Inspection; Healthy Children Kickoff, Lamar and Honey Alexander Visit the Maternal and Infant Care Unit; Ed Asner, September 29, 1983 (Box 12)
    - National Commission on Excellence in Education in Kingsport, Tennessee, September 30, 1983 (Box 12)
    - (2 Folders) Proclamations; National Commission on Excellence in Education, Kingsport, Tennessee; Statewide Textbook Commission Meeting; Swearing in of Ernest Pellegrin, October 3, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Oakmont School and PTO Chili Supper, October 14, 1983 (Box 12)
    - 33rd Annual Tennessee Teacher of the Year Awards Banquet, October 17, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Interview, October 18, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Nissan Dedication Ceremony, October 21, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Proclamations, October 26, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Visiting the Set of “The River”, November 1, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Presentation, Proposed New Dollars for Education, November 4, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Support Your Public School, Central Middle School, Murfreesboro, November 8, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Annual Veterans Day Parade, November 11, 1983 (Box 12)
    - 3rd Annual Student Congress on Public Education, November 17, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Proclamation for Family Life Week, November 18, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Party, November 20, 1983 (Box 12)
    - MNEA Poster Contest Winner; Southern Regional Education Board, November 21, 1983 (Box 12)
    - (3 Folders) Cades Cove, November 25-27, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Governor Alexander and Family and Christmas Tree, November 29, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Christmas Tree, December 1, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Convention; Warner Elementary School Students, December 6, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Food Services Christmas Lunch, December 14, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Proclamations, December 15, 1983 (Box 12)
    - (Contact Sheets), December 19, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Santa Claus, Birthday Party, December 20, 1983 (Box 12)
    - (Contact Sheets), December 21, 1983 (Box 12)
  - Photographs, Chronological
    - Press Conference, January 3, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Special Session News Conference, January 4, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Budget Address, January 10, 1984 (Box 13)
    - (Contact Sheet), January 13, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Legislative Interns, January 16, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Proclamations, January 18, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Senator Baker, Representative Don Sundquist, Representative Jimmy Quillen, Representative Duncan, January 19, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Pride of Tennessee Certificate Presented to Mildred Doyle, January 20, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Scouting Anniversary Week, January 25, 1984 (Box 13)
    - (Contact Sheet), January 26, 1984 (Box 13)
    - (2 Folders) Governor Alexander Delivers 3rd Annual State of Education Address, January 27, 1984 (Box 13)
    - (2 Folders) Swearing in of Martha Olsen, Commissioner of Department of Personnel, and Don Jackson, Commissioner of Department of Revenue; Charlie Daniels; Proclamations, January 31, 1984 (Box 13)
    - (Contact Sheet), February 1, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Conference about Computer, February 2, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Proclamation for Selective Service Registration Awareness Month, February 3, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Vocational Education Week, February 6, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Lenoir City High School Students, February 9, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Legislative Assembly; John Parish and Corporate Representatives from Central Soya of Chattanooga, Inc., February 15, 1984 (Box 13)
    - YMCA Youth in Government; Teachers’ Study Council, February 16, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Lamar Alexander with Students; Lamar Alexander with Girl Scouts, February 21, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Austin Peay Computer Lab; Special Session Final News Conference, February 23, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Victor Ashe, March 5, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Signing Ceremony for SB 1/HB 1 (Comprehensive Education Reform Act of 1984) and SB 3/HB 7 (Sales Tax), Julia Green Elementary School, March 6, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Tennessee Tomorrow Students, Farragut High School, March 7, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Miss Tennessee, Moira Kaye; Proclamation, National Surveyors Week, March 8, 1984 (Box 13)
    - State Board of Education Meeting; SEC Referees, March 9, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Swearing in of Senator Earl Sharp; Rep. Bill McAfee and Two Priests, March 21, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Future Farmers of America Tennessee State Officers, March 26, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Employee Service Awards; Rep. Person and Christ Methodist Day School Students; Oliver Springs High School Students, March 28, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Proclamations; Glenwood School Students, March 29, 1984 (Box 13)
    - State Board Confirmation Hearing, April 2, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Bill Signing HB 33/SB 589 (Equal Access to Justice); United Tennessee Veterans Association Reception, April 3, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Senator Hamilton, Ned Ray McWherter and 2 pages, April 4, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Peter Jenkins, Minnie Pearl, and Ron Terry, April 5, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Judge Inman; Film Tape and Music, April 9, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Service Awards; George Kelly and ETSU Reporting Public Affairs Class, April 10, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Senator Leonard C. Dunavant and Memphis State University Singers; Farragut Middle School Students, April 11, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Alcoa High School Students, April 12, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Lamar Alexander in Japan, April 23, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Bill Signing SB 1878/HB 1640 (Coon Dog Bill); Representative Chiles and Overton Band Officers; Winfield Elementary School Students, April 25, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Hillwood High School, April 26, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Governor Alexander with Unknown People, April 27, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Governor Alexander and Nelson Andrews, Chairman of the State Board of Education, April 28, 1984 (Box 13)
  - Photographs, Chronological
    - Service Awards, May 1, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Governor’s Prayer Breakfast, May 3, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Tennessee Summer of Coke Tourism Promotion, May 4, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Office Birthday Party, May 5, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Bill Signing, May 9, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Governor Alexander Addresses Select Committee on Health Care Cost Containment; Indian Lake Elementary School Students, May 10, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Governor Alexander and Nissan Motors President Marvin Runyon Exchange Handshake across a Nissan Sentra; Press Conference at Nissan Plant, May 11, 1984 (Box 14)
    - (2 Folders) Reelfoot Lake Groundbreaking Ceremony at Hornbeak for Silt Detention Dam; Fishing on Reelfoot Lake, May 12, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Governor Alexander Holds Olympic Torch, May 15, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Governor’s Business Forum, May 16, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Governor Alexander and National Boys Club, May 18, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Signing of HB 1598 with Rep. Walter Work; Presentation of Resolution Honoring Ed Moody; Representative Buddy Scruggs and Interns; Senator Buzz Elkins and Intern, May 22, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Swearing In of Rick Sivley; Meeting in Cabinet Room, May 23, 1984 (Box 14)
    - (2 Folders) Tennessee General Assembly Special Session on Education Reform, Voting On Comprehensive Education Reform Act (composite photo), News Conference; Signing of HB 1785; Signing of HB 661;Retiring House Members; Governor Alexander and Interns, May 24, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Children on Capitol Steps, May 25, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Olympic Torch Relay, May 29, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Bill Signing with Representative Cobb, May 31, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Signing of HB 1977 (Judicial Reform Bill); Signing of HB 1603; Signing of SB 1517, June 1, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Signing of Martin Luther King Bill; Signing of Forestry Bill; Beauty Contest Winner, June 5, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Bill Signing, June 13, 1984 (Box 14)
    - (4 Folders) 50 Year Anniversary Celebration of Great Smoky Mountains National Park; Governor Alexander Hiking in Smoky Mountains, June 15, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Swearing In of Bill Koch; Swearing In of Lewis Lavine, June 18, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Tennessee Arts Commission Reception at Residence, June 19, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Homecoming ’86 T-Shirt, June 22, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Governor Alexander, Representative Randy McNally, and Others, June 27, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Governor Alexander with Cliff Frensley; Governor Alexander and Ray Clark, July 5, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Presentation of 40 Year Service Award, July 6, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Press Conference, July 13, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Governor’s Schedule – No Photos, July 14, 1984 (Box 14)
    - McGavock High School Baseball Team; Sen. Henry and Group from Taiwan; Education Forum-Humanities Institute for Secondary School Principals, July 17, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Governor’s Report; Governor Alexander and Minnie Pearl Discuss Plans for Homecoming Celebration; Governor Alexander and Dan Tankersley Discuss Vegetable Program, July 18, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Bill Signing, July 26, 1984 (Box 14)
  - Photographs, Chronological
    - 7th Annual Tennessee Safety Congress, August 6, 1984 (Box 15)
    - GOP Post-Convention Picnic; Governor Alexander and Children; Governor Alexander, Ronnie Davis and Judge Inman, August 27, 1984 (Box 15)
    - Passport Pictures of Lamar Alexander and Honey Alexander, August 29, 1984 (Box 15)
    - Governor’s Office, August 31, 1984 (Box 15)
    - Visit to Schools, September 4, 1984 (Box 15)
    - Visit to Schools (Composite); Visit to Caldwell Magnet School; Visit to Westview High School; Visit to UT Martin; Weakley County Better Schools Day, September 5, 1984 (Box 15)
    - Visit to Schools, September 6, 1984 (Box 15)
    - President Reagan Visits Tennessee (Composite), Roy Acuff Birthday Celebration, Minnie Pearl at Grand Ole Opry, Tennessee Technology Foundation Meeting, September 13, 1984 (Box 15)
    - Corrections, Morgan County Escapees Prison Photos; Governor Alexander with Individuals in Office, September 14, 1984 (Box 15)
    - Proclamation for Sight Saving Month with Ronnie Milsap; Governor Alexander with Intern, September 17, 1984 (Box 15)
    - Tourism Conference and Governor’s Luncheon, Dinosaur Replicas, September 20, 1984 (Box 15)
    - School Visits in Sparta, September 21, 1984 (Box 15)
    - Meeting with Representatives of ABC Affiliates, September 24, 1984 (Box 15)
    - State Dinner at Residence, September 27, 1984 (Box 15)
    - Visit to Newport Grammar School; School Leadership Meeting; Visit to Parrottsville Elementary School, October 1, 1984 (Box 15)
    - Headshots of Philip Davidson, Department of Safety, October 2, 1984 (Box 15)
    - Judge Inman, October 3, 1984 (Box 15)
    - Proclamations; Salute to America, October 9, 1984 (Box 15)
    - Visit to Bradley Elementary School; Visit to MTSU; Visit to Oakland High School, October 22, 1984 (Box 15)
    - Governor Alexander and Senator Ernest Crouch, October 23, 1984 (Box 15)
    - Montgomery County Education Task Force Meeting; Overton County Task Force Meeting, October 24, 1984 (Box 15)
    - Visit to Sam Houston Elementary School; Meeting with Task Force; Visit to Wilson County Vocation Center, October 25, 1984 (Box 15)
    - McNairy County Task Force Meeting; Proclamations, October 29, 1984 (Box 15)
    - Wayne County Task Force Meeting, November 7, 1984 (Box 15)
    - Governor Alexander with Senator-Elect Al Gore with Reporters, November 11, 1984 (Box 15)
    - Jane Whitson Award; Dairy Trophy Presentation; Overton Band Officers, November 14, 1984 (Box 15)
    - Visit to Bluff City Middle School; Visit to Avoca Elementary School; Visit to Dobyns Bennett High School; State Dinner, November 15, 1984 (Box 15)
    - Visit to Eastside Elementary School; Visit to Brownsville School, November 19, 1984 (Box 15)
    - State Technical Institute at Knoxville Dinner; Commissioner Ward, November 20, 1984 (Box 15)
    - Press Conference, November 21, 1984 (Box 15)
    - Visit to Oneida Elementary School; Visit to Scott County High School, November 26, 1984 (Box 15)
    - (2 Folders) Governor’s Community Luncheon, Community Exhibits, November 28, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Photographs, Chronological
    - 63rd Annual Convention of the Tennessee Farm Bureau Federation, December 4, 1984 (Box 16)
    - (2 Folders) William Blount High School Students; James Wakefield Burke Presenting Book about Davy Crockett; Lamar Alexander Carving Turkey in Cafeteria; Presentation of South Central Bell Phone Book; First Family’s Christmas Card, December 6, 1984 (Box 16)
    - School Visits: Decaturville Elementary School, Scotts Hill School, Riverside High School, December 11, 1984 (Box 16)
    - I & A Board Meeting; Portrait Photos; Lamar Alexander and Jim Varney, December 12, 1984 (Box 16)
    - Lamar Alexander Playing Piano, December 16, 1984 (Box 16)
    - Meeting of the Electoral College; Giles County Task Force Meeting; Service Awards, December 17, 1984 (Box 16)
    - Businessmen from Komatsu; Clay County Task Force Meeting; Christmas Sing, December 18, 1984 (Box 16)
    - Christmas Luncheon, December 19, 1984 (Box 16)
    - Bill Long and Tappan Officials, January 4, 1985 (Box 16)
    - Lamar Alexander Photo, January 7, 1985 (Box 16)
    - Seminar for County Officials; Governor Alexander with Congressmen; Representative Duer, January 8, 1985 (Box 16)